http://www.lymphomainfo.net/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
At LymphomaInfo.net we understand the importance of protecting your privacy. Our Privacy Policy covers our treatment of personal information collected when anyone is on our site or uses the services we provide; it neither addresses nor applies to individuals or third party practices over which we have no control. This includes, but is not limited to, cookies which may be used by our advertisers.
LymphomaInfo.net only collects information pertinent to our website; as such, our stated goal is to customize your experience and let you get the most out of what we offer. To that end:
1.	LymphomaInfo.net will never rent, share, distribute, or sell any of the personal information you provide.
2.	For your security and privacy, your information is protected with a password created by you.
3.	You will always have access to your personal information and you may edit or delete it at any time.
4.	In an effort to protect children, users must be 13 years old to use our Support Groups.
Information Collection and Use:
Information Collected Upon Registration:
When you create or reconfigure a user account with LymphomaInfo.net, you provide some personal information, such as your username, password, and email address. Some of this information (i.e. your username and profile picture) is listed publicly on our Website, including on your profile page and in search results. Some Services, such as search, do not require registration.
Email Communications with Us:
As part of the Services, you may receive email and other communications from us. Administrative communications relating to your Account (e.g., for purposes of Account recovery or password reset) are considered part of the Services and your Account, which you may not be able to opt-out from receiving. We also may send you other kinds of emails, which you can opt-out of either from your Account Settings page or by using the “Opt-Out” link in the emails themselves. Note that we will never email you to ask for your password or other Account Information; if you receive such an email, please forward it to us.
Additional Information:
You may provide us with profile information to make public, such as a short biography, your zipcode, your birthdate, or a picture. Your account settings control whether others can see your birthday. If you email us, we may keep your message, email address and contact information to respond to your request. Providing the additional information described in this section is entirely optional.
Posts, Comments, Replies, Following, Groups and other Public Information:
Our Services are primarily designed to help you share information and get support. Most of the information you provide us is information you are asking us to make public. This includes not only the posts and comments you create and the metadata provided therein, such as when you commented, but also the members you follow and many other bits of information that result from your use of the Services. Our default is almost always to make the information you provide public for as long as you do not delete it from LymphomaInfo.net. Your public posts and comments may be searchable by search engines. When you share information or content like photos, videos, and posts via the Services, you should think carefully about what you are making public.
Cookies:
Like many websites, we use "cookie" technology to collect additional website usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as searching and looking at public user profiles or lists. A cookie is a small data file that is transferred to your computer's hard disk. LymphomaInfo.net may use both session cookies and persistent cookies to better understand how you interact with our Services, to monitor aggregate usage by our users and web traffic routing on our Services, and to customize and improve our Services. Most Internet browsers automatically accept cookies. You can instruct your browser, by changing its settings, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. However, some Services may not function properly if you disable cookies.
Log Data:
Our servers automatically record information ("Log Data") created by your use of the Services. Log Data may include information such as your IP address, browser type, operating system, the referring web page, pages visited, location, your mobile carrier, device and application IDs, search terms, and cookie information. We receive Log Data when you interact with our Services, for example, when you visit our websites, sign into our Services, or interact with our email notifications. LymphomaInfo.net uses Log Data to provide our Services and to measure, customize, and improve them. If not already done earlier, for example, as provided below, we will either delete Log Data or remove any common account identifiers, such as your username, full IP address, or email address, after 18 months.
Information Sharing and Disclosure
Law and Harm:
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary in this Policy, we may preserve or disclose your information if we believe that it is reasonably necessary to comply with a law, regulation or legal request; to protect the safety of any person; to address fraud, security or technical issues; or to protect LymphomaInfo.net’s rights or property. However, nothing in this Privacy Policy is intended to limit any legal defenses or objections that you may have to a third party’s, including a government’s request to disclose your information.
Business Transfers:
In the event that LymphomaInfo.net is involved in a bankruptcy, merger, acquisition, reorganization or sale of assets, your information may be sold or transferred as part of that transaction. The promises in this Privacy Policy will apply to your information as transferred to the new entity.
Non-Private or Non-Personal Information:
We may share or disclose your non-private, aggregated or otherwise non-personal information, such as your public user profile information.
Modifying Your Personal Information
If you are a registered user of our Services, we provide you with tools and account settings to access or modify the personal information you provided to us and associated with your account.
You can also permanently delete your LymphomaInfo.net account. Please email us at info@toseekemedia.com to delete your posts and delete your account at the same time.
Note: LymphomaInfo.net changes your settings immediately. However, old links may appear on Google and other search engines because they have cached old content in their search index. LymphomaInfo.net has no control over this, but you can send search engines a request to take down your information.
Our Policy Towards Children
Our Services are not directed to persons under 13. If you become aware that your child has provided us with personal information without your consent, please contact us at site@toseekmedia.com. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If we become aware that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we take steps to remove such information and terminate the child's account.
Changes & Conditions of Use
Changes or amendments to our Privacy Policy may occur now and again as warranted. However, information is always and only subject to the policy in place at the time it is collected. Should we feel the need to execute a change in the Policy, we will announce the change on our website so that our users are made aware of the change and may act accordingly.
Finally, the conditions of use (visits to our website, including the information collected, our use of that information, and any future disputes regarding issues of privacy) are subject to both this Policy and our Terms of Use.
Effective: 06/26/19
site@toseekmedia.com
2740 St. James Rd.
Belmont, CA 94002
More Articles
Lymphoma
Is There Such A Thing As A Benign Lymphoma?
Surviving Lymphoma
The Difference Between Relapsed Lymphoma and Refractory Lymphoma
Surviving Lymphoma
T Cell Lymphoma Survival Rate: Brief Look At The Broad Groups
B-Cell
Testicular Lymphoma: Symptoms, Diagnosis, Prognosis, and Treatment
Lymphoma
The Pathophysiology of Lymphoma: Signs and Symptoms That Are Identified
Non-hodgkins Lymphoma
How is Mesenteric Lymphoma Diagnosed?
How is Mesenteric Lymphoma Diagnosed?
This entry looks at what is sometimes referred to as mesenteric lymphoma, also referred to as non-Hodgkin's...
T-Cell
T Cell Lymphoma: Causes, Classification, and Diagnosis
In T cell lymphoma, T lymphocytes, which are an essential part of the body's immune response, become malignant. T cell lymphomas account for about...
Symptoms
Low Lymphoma White Blood Cell Count & Lymphoma Symptoms
Lymphoma is a cancer affecting the white blood cells (lymphocytes) of the body's immune system. The cells begin to grow abnormally and much faster...
Chemotherapy
What Is The RICE Cancer Treatment?
RICE is an acronym for an anti-cancer treatment that expresses a combination chemotherapeutic regimen. This regimen is written variously as "R+ICE...
Surviving Lymphoma
B Cell Lymphoma Survival Rate and Life Expectancy: Revised International Prognostic Index
B cell lymphoma is not one disease but a few dozen heterogeneous diseases, or individual cancers, that affect the b...
Mantle Cell
Mantle Cell Lymphoma Life Expectancy Depends On Various Factors
Mantle cell lymphoma (MCL) is just one of 50-60 known B-cell subtypes of...
Causes
What Are Some of The Causes of Lymphoma?
What causes lymphoma is not well known. DNA mutations may be what causes lymphoma to develop but what triggers these mutations is...
B-Cell
B-Cell Lymphoma Types: In-Depth List of Lymphoma Classifications
A B cell is a type of lymphocyte that produces antibodies to fight infections. These are the most prevalent lymphocytes in the bloodstream and are...
Prognosis
Stage 4 Hodgkin's Lymphoma Prognosis
Also known as Hodgkin's disease, Hodgkin's lymphoma (HL) is a cancer of the white blood cells, or...
Animals
Lymphoma in Dogs: What Is The Prognosis and Treatment?
Canine lymphoma, just like lymphoma in humans, can be separated into stages,...
Surviving Lymphoma
Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma Survival Rate by Stage
This article looks at the Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma survival rate as well as the Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma mortality rate ....
T-Cell
What is T-Cell Lymphoblastic Lymphoma?
T-Cell Lymphoblastic Lymphoma (T-LBL) is a very rare subtype of non-Hodgkin's lymphoma. It tends to develop in...
Symptoms
Causes and Treatment of Lymphoma Itching
It's not uncommon for patients with some lymphomas to experience itching (clinically known as pruritus). Lymphoma itching symptoms can range from...
T-Cell
B-cell Lymphoma vs. T-cell Lymphoma: What Are The Differences Between The Two?
In non-Hodgkin's lymphoma, you have your B-cell lymphomas and you have your T-cell lymphomas.
Why B...
Surviving Lymphoma
Maintenance Rituximab Therapy Improves Survival
More Articles
Chemotherapy
What Is The RICE Cancer Treatment?
Surviving Lymphoma
B Cell Lymphoma Survival Rate and Life Expectancy: Revised International Prognostic Index
Mantle Cell
Mantle Cell Lymphoma Life Expectancy Depends On Various Factors
Causes
What Are Some of The Causes of Lymphoma?
B-Cell
B-Cell Lymphoma Types: In-Depth List of Lymphoma Classifications
Prognosis
Stage 4 Hodgkin's Lymphoma Prognosis
Animals
Lymphoma in Dogs: What Is The Prognosis and Treatment?
Surviving Lymphoma
Non-Hodgkin's Lymphoma Survival Rate by Stage
Lymphoma
The Pathophysiology of Lymphoma: Signs and Symptoms That Are Identified
Non-hodgkins Lymphoma
How is Mesenteric Lymphoma Diagnosed?
Is There Such A Thing As A Benign Lymphoma?
Surviving Lymphoma
The Difference Between Relapsed Lymphoma and Refractory Lymphoma
Surviving Lymphoma
T Cell Lymphoma Survival Rate: Brief Look At The Broad Groups
More Articles
More Articles
B-Cell
Testicular Lymphoma: Symptoms, Diagnosis, Prognosis, and Treatment
Lymphoma
The Pathophysiology of Lymphoma: Signs and Symptoms That Are Identified
Non-hodgkins Lymphoma
How is Mesenteric Lymphoma Diagnosed?
What Is The RICE Cancer Treatment?
